Commanders family, welcome in to another
free agency Fridays here in the command
center big bear AI command center
studio. I'm yours Brian Kova Jr. here
with one of our free agents, a resigning
free agent, our guy Chris Paul, man.
Welcome to the building, brother.
>> Thank you, brother.
>> This your first time in the studio.
>> Second.
>> Second time, man. First things first,
congratulations, man. Just put pen to
paper, man. How are you feeling?
>> I feel great. It's a blessing. It's a
full circle moment. I mean, I did this
as a rookie
>> four years ago. Great. So, it's really
cool.
>> And this is your first time being able
to see what free agency is like, going
out there, seeing your value, having
teams calling you, having the commander
saying, "Hey, we need you back." Man,
what was that like?
>> It was crazy. Crazy. I mean, I I felt
like I experienced every spectrum of the
of emotion, you know what I mean?
>> Um, and it it was fun. It was it was
nerve-wracking. Um, and I just I knew
that
however it panned out, I was always
going to lean towards being home.
>> Yeah. And this has become home, man.
What makes this feel like home for you,
man? You've been through a lot and like
you said, those first four years. Last
year was a little different. What makes
this feel like home for you?
>> Cuz I mean, like you said, I've just
I've been through a lot. I've
experienced so much change in this very
building. Um, the first time you
interviewed me, it wasn't even in the
space that we're in right now.
>> Whole studio.
>> Whole different studio. So, um, I think
just when you get to experience
all that change and you get to
experience the continued growth that
this organization morphs into, that
really means something to you and it
really means something to me. And so,
that that's why this is home. And
>> it's not just the organization growing.
It's not just the organization changing.
You've grown and changed in your four
years here. How have you grown and
changed? I' I've just I feel like I'm
just scratching the surface of the
player I can be. And that's actually the
most exciting part. And I saw tremendous
growth in last year from the way that I
approached off season, from the way that
I approached
meetings and film study and practice and
communication and being comfortable
leading and being comfortable
making sure we're all on the same page
and
really bonding with the brotherhood that
we have. Um, I've seen tremendous
growth.
>> What has aided in that growth? Is it
just time, right? Is just you feeling
more comfortable or have you been
watching others? Have others kind of
helped you along the way to realize,
okay, these are the things you need to
do to take the next step.
>> Absolutely. I think um it's it's time.
It's it's time on task. also think
I like to consider myself like a sponge
and
I I love to just soak up the tidbits,
information, life lessons, advice that I
get from vets. Like there's vets from my
rookie year that I still keep in contact
with, still ask for advice, still
remember the advice that they've already
given me. And I just I I keep that going
and I hope to to be the one to pay that
forward to players younger than me.
>> And the guy in Laramie Tonsel just had a
press conference and I don't know if you
saw it but was showing you a lot of
love. He said, "Thank God we brought him
back." He was like, "I don't even know
if I'm allowed to say this, but man, I
really wanted Chris Paul back. He talked
about your guys' relationship on and off
the field. What you guys have bonded
together, man. That's one of the best to
ever do it." Talking about you and
saying, "Thank God he's back. Thank God
he's going to be right next to me
possibly. How great is that, man? How
How does that feel?
>> That feels great. I mean, and I've I've
I've said this before, but one of the
biggest honors I think a player can
receive is
praise or positive judgment from your
peers and your brothers that play with
you. I mean,
>> it it doesn't get any better than that.
And I've told Laramie personally, but
it's been one of the greatest honors of
my life to play next to him.
>> Wow.
>> And um
>> I'm just excited for the opportunity to
keep that going.
>> And you didn't know what last year was
going to be like at this point, right?
Coming into it in the off season and
then I think a few games in you get your
chance to start.
>> Yep.
>> How ready were you for that moment?
Because things go so fast, right? Things
happen so quickly. Nothing's promised in
this NFL. You get that starting nod and
then it's just full speed, man. What was
that moment like for you?
>> I mean, it was it was great. I I was
just I was so excited. Um, and I was
most importantly I was ready
>> and I believe that showed I was I was
ready to
showcase the player I can be and and
beyond. And so, um, I'm I'm just really
again super grateful for the
opportunity. It's something I I never
take lightly. And it's it's an honor.
And
>> now you're back in the building. You got
paid, but nothing's promised, man.
You're still going to be out here
battling. But that's nothing new to you.
You have been battling since you got in
this building. Talk about being
prepared. How have you prepared yourself
for this new step, this new journey, and
>> it's your spot to lose, man. So, I'm
sure that's pretty exciting.
>> It's It's super exciting. And um yeah,
it's one of the things that I appreciate
about this organization is the emphasis
of just competition.
>> Competition. I think as a player that I
would say for me personally, that's what
excites me most most about the game is
you're always getting the opportunity to
compete and you always have to prove
yourself every year and you have to keep
proving yourself every year, every game.
And there there's comfort in sort of
knowing that you have to earn everything
that you have.
>> And so, um, that's something that I I
never lose. And I'm just I'm so excited
to get after it again this year.
>> Yeah. And you've earned everything, man.
And then you look at this David Blau
offense and what we're expecting to see.
And it seems as if the guard play is
very, very important in this offense.
That athleticism, being able to run
around more. So, you smile a little bit
as you think about it. How are you the
perfect guard for this new offensive
we're about to
>> I mean, I'm I'm so excited. Move
movement's going to be huge.
>> Powerful play is going to be huge.
>> Um, and that's something especially as a
O line, especially as a guard that you
you take pride in. And I'm I'm happy for
Blau and I I'm so excited to just
witness the offense that he's assembling
>> and it's going to be a great time.
>> And we talk about last year and all the
cool things you got to do. To me, the
coolest thing that I think I saw in the
NFL last year was seeing you and your
brother out in Spain share that feel
together. Man, I know that was probably
major for you as a big brother, probably
major for your family, your parents
watching this, man. Can you just put
into words what it's been like seeing
your brother on these NFL fields sharing
this journey with you?
>> It's it's been
the coolest
experience of my life. It might be the
coolest experience of my life and um
I'm just so proud of him and the way
that we both just inspire each other to
be better. Um, I played at Tulsa, he
played at Houston. So, there were times
in college that we got to play against
each other. So,
you know, preeason 2024 and Madrid in
2025, those were full circle moments of
like getting to do that same thing
again, right?
>> And it's it's just so cool. Our entire
family was there and they were just
beaming with immense pride to get to do
something that that feels like a once in
a lifetime moment and I just I love him.
I love him and I'm so proud of him.
>> It's crazy cuz the first time we spoke
you were talking about your brother. He
was still in college and you were
talking about how excited you were to
see him in the NFL, how he was going to
be one of the ones you knew. Yeah, man.
That's crazy. did. You've been like a
mentor to him as his big brother, but
then also going into year four, you've
also got to help other young guys along
the way. You got a guy Josh Connelly Jr.
where I talked to you, I talked to
Laramie. All of you guys seem like that
that quiet,
>> scary confidence that you guys have,
man. Like, I haven't seen nothing like
it. What has it been like watching a
young guy like Josh Conley Jr. get into
his own?
>> Man,
he's elite.
>> Yeah, he is. He's elite. And it's it's
it was so cool to watch him grow
throughout his rookie year. And I think
a lot of people forget that that's
really what the game is all about. And
he's just scratching the surface of a
player that he can be. And I'm I'm so
excited to get to play on this team with
him. and and I'm so excited to just
watch the huge steps that he's going to
take in year two and beyond,
>> man. Bro, congratulations on everything,
man. We going to let you get up out of
here cuz we know you got to go
celebrate, man. Got some new money to
spin, my G. Last question for you,
though. Are you still making music, man?
Are we going to get a new song? We going
to get a new track, you know, now that
you got a little more inspiration, a
little more motivation.
>> Hey, man. Stay stay tuned on that front.
>> Okay, we love that for sure, man. Chris,
congratulations again, man. Nothing's
promised in the NFL, but you made it
here and you earned it, brother. So,
congrats.
>> Thank you, brother.
>> Commanders family, our next man up, part
of Free Fridays, Chris Paul is back in
the building to run it back with the
Burgundy and Gold. Congrats, fam. Yes,
sir.